[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "\"Viva Rock Vegas\"?", "question_tokens": ["``", "Viva", "Rock", "Vegas", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "You're not kidding.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "kidding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Blu-Ray?", "question_tokens": ["Blu-Ray", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "That's exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "That's on the card, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "on", "the", "card", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "No, it's not on the card.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "on", "the", "card", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["a half years ago"]}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "But you never did stand-up?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "never", "did", "stand-up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I didn't start until about three and a half years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "start", "until", "about", "three", "and", "a", "half", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "What do you do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "I do colleges.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "colleges", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Do you still do it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["three years ago"]}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Would you do it ever again?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "do", "it", "ever", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "'DONNELL: You know, actually I went back about three years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["'DONNELL", ":", "You", "know", ",", "actually", "I", "went", "back", "about", "three", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "How many kids in your family?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "kids", "in", "your", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "There are three.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Loyola Center"], "LOCATION": ["Rome", "Chicago", "Illinois", "Chicago", "Loyola Chicago"]}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "You were born in Rome, Italy?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "born", "in", "Rome", ",", "Italy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "CHALE: My dad was the dean of students at the Loyola Center, Rome campus, for Chicago, Illinois -- Chicago, Loyola Chicago.", "answer_tokens": ["CHALE", ":", "My", "dad", "was", "the", "dean", "of", "students", "at", "the", "Loyola", "Center", ",", "Rome", "campus", ",", "for", "Chicago", ",", "Illinois", "--", "Chicago", ",", "Loyola", "Chicago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Rome", "Italy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "And were you Oliver?", "question_tokens": ["And", "were", "you", "Oliver", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "And you enjoy singing, I take it, if that was a musical production?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "enjoy", "singing", ",", "I", "take", "it", ",", "if", "that", "was", "a", "musical", "production", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Well, it was a kids' production, so they would take just about anything.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "a", "kids", "'", "production", ",", "so", "they", "would", "take", "just", "about", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "And in high school, you were athletic, I take it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "high", "school", ",", "you", "were", "athletic", ",", "I", "take", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "I played a lot of sports.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "played", "a", "lot", "of", "sports", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "The singers, FOX?", "question_tokens": ["The", "singers", ",", "FOX", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Yes, OK.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "In college, as well?", "question_tokens": ["In", "college", ",", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Yes, not well.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "not", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "You didn't?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "I didn't hear that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "hear", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Didn't you tweet something?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "you", "tweet", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "She tweeted me that she was going to watch the -- she was going to go on a date.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "tweeted", "me", "that", "she", "was", "going", "to", "watch", "the", "--", "she", "was", "going", "to", "go", "on", "a", "date", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "How did you do that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "We thought, actually, that was too many days, when we told the joke.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "thought", ",", "actually", ",", "that", "was", "too", "many", "days", ",", "when", "we", "told", "the", "joke", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "And is it awkward and weird?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "it", "awkward", "and", "weird", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "No, because she's really nice and charismatic.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "she", "'s", "really", "nice", "and", "charismatic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Ryan Seacrest?", "question_tokens": ["Ryan", "Seacrest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "He's right here.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "right", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Seacrest"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "But you're actually friendly with him, yes?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "'re", "actually", "friendly", "with", "him", ",", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "We are friendly.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "friendly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Has anyone ever become very angry and contacted you?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "anyone", "ever", "become", "very", "angry", "and", "contacted", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Without exception, no one has said you're going down.", "answer_tokens": ["Without", "exception", ",", "no", "one", "has", "said", "you", "'re", "going", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "As often as possible?", "question_tokens": ["As", "often", "as", "possible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "No matter how badly we make fun of them.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "matter", "how", "badly", "we", "make", "fun", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "I was one of the legion of fans that was saying what happened?", "question_tokens": ["I", "was", "one", "of", "the", "legion", "of", "fans", "that", "was", "saying", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBG", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Bless you.", "answer_tokens": ["Bless", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Can we put -- well, no, it said something like -- doesn't it say things about the person as they're down there?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "put", "--", "well", ",", "no", ",", "it", "said", "something", "like", "--", "does", "n't", "it", "say", "things", "about", "the", "person", "as", "they", "'re", "down", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Sometimes it does.", "answer_tokens": ["Sometimes", "it", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", ":", "DT", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Stud muffin?", "question_tokens": ["Stud", "muffin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "I sort of feel like -- no, like doesn't like ice in his drinks.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "sort", "of", "feel", "like", "--", "no", ",", "like", "does", "n't", "like", "ice", "in", "his", "drinks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Sore gums?", "question_tokens": ["Sore", "gums", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "-- citrus fruit.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "citrus", "fruit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "UH", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "That's just a happy day, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "just", "a", "happy", "day", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Oh, it was a -- I was OK with it.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "was", "a", "--", "I", "was", "OK", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "RBR", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "What kind of a dad are you, strict?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "a", "dad", "are", "you", ",", "strict", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I -- my wife is way more even keel.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "my", "wife", "is", "way", "more", "even", "keel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "And where did you meet?", "question_tokens": ["And", "where", "did", "you", "meet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "And well, I mean I gave the kid cigarettes just a few years ago, because I'm like I don't even want to start on this.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "well", ",", "I", "mean", "I", "gave", "the", "kid", "cigarettes", "just", "a", "few", "years", "ago", ",", "because", "I", "'m", "like", "I", "do", "n't", "even", "want", "to", "start", "on", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rosie"]}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Has fame affected your ability to be out in public with your family?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "fame", "affected", "your", "ability", "to", "be", "out", "in", "public", "with", "your", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Oh, it's so hard, Rosie.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "'s", "so", "hard", ",", "Rosie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Not at all?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "It's not -- it's not bad.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "--", "it", "'s", "not", "bad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PDT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "And didn't you promise to French kiss every man and woman who participated?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "n't", "you", "promise", "to", "French", "kiss", "every", "man", "and", "woman", "who", "participated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Every man and woman, I will French kiss, for all that.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "man", "and", "woman", ",", "I", "will", "French", "kiss", ",", "for", "all", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Who did you look up to and go, hey, that's the person I'd like to be like?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "did", "you", "look", "up", "to", "and", "go", ",", "hey", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "person", "I", "'d", "like", "to", "be", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Now have you ever met any one of these people and then been star struck?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "have", "you", "ever", "met", "any", "one", "of", "these", "people", "and", "then", "been", "star", "struck", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Well, I did it -- yes, I'm totally.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "it", "--", "yes", ",", "I", "'m", "totally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "JJR", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "And was he as you had imagined?", "question_tokens": ["And", "was", "he", "as", "you", "had", "imagined", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "He was that and more so.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "that", "and", "more", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Are your kids funny?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "your", "kids", "funny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "He does?", "question_tokens": ["He", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "It's pretty great.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "pretty", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Four?", "question_tokens": ["Four", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "And I love it.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 559, "question": "'DONNELL: You would?", "question_tokens": ["'DONNELL", ":", "You", "would", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Come on, is she amazing?", "question_tokens": ["Come", "on", ",", "is", "she", "amazing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "A legend.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "legend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Were you ever mad?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "ever", "mad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "No, I thought it was hysterical.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "hysterical", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Watch \"Community,\" will you?", "question_tokens": ["Watch", "``", "Community", ",", "''", "will", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "``", "NN", ",", "''", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Let's hope it does well.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "hope", "it", "does", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Please stay, will you?", "question_tokens": ["Please", "stay", ",", "will", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I'm staying for that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "staying", "for", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rosie"]}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Anjelica, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Anjelica", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "I'm great, Rosie.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "great", ",", "Rosie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "How perfect is the show?", "question_tokens": ["How", "perfect", "is", "the", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "It's fantastic.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "fantastic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "This is the first time that you've done series TV, yes?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "first", "time", "that", "you", "'ve", "done", "series", "TV", ",", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Are we going to get to see Ilene sing finally?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "going", "to", "get", "to", "see", "Ilene", "sing", "finally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "We are.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ilene"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scott Wittman", "Marc Shaiman"]}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Was it nerve racking when you had to do that?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "nerve", "racking", "when", "you", "had", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "Totally nerve racking but we have two amazing composers on the series, Scott Wittman and Marc Shaiman and they got me through it.", "answer_tokens": ["Totally", "nerve", "racking", "but", "we", "have", "two", "amazing", "composers", "on", "the", "series", ",", "Scott", "Wittman", "and", "Marc", "Shaiman", "and", "they", "got", "me", "through", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Raul"]}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ":", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "POS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "And actually -- god, what was it called, our tango, Raul's and my tango and --", "answer_tokens": ["And", "actually", "--", "god", ",", "what", "was", "it", "called", ",", "our", "tango", ",", "Raul", "'s", "and", "my", "tango", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "In the \"Addams Family\"?", "question_tokens": ["In", "the", "``", "Addams", "Family", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "USTON: Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["USTON", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "Well, when they asked you to do this, what made you consider coming to New York and doing series TV?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "they", "asked", "you", "to", "do", "this", ",", "what", "made", "you", "consider", "coming", "to", "New", "York", "and", "doing", "series", "TV", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Well, first of all, the writing on the series was so good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "the", "writing", "on", "the", "series", "was", "so", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "So your husband Robert who everyone loved, tremendous artist and he passed away about three years ago now?", "question_tokens": ["So", "your", "husband", "Robert", "who", "everyone", "loved", ",", "tremendous", "artist", "and", "he", "passed", "away", "about", "three", "years", "ago", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "WP", "NN", "VBD", ",", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "And that must have been very difficult to imagine how to move forward?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "must", "have", "been", "very", "difficult", "to", "imagine", "how", "to", "move", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "It was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 803, "question": "Does she sing a ballad when she gets to sing?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "sing", "a", "ballad", "when", "she", "gets", "to", "sing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 804, "answer": "She sings a little something her grandfather used to sing.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "sings", "a", "little", "something", "her", "grandfather", "used", "to", "sing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 806, "question": "Did you feel pushed or drawn or pulled?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "pushed", "or", "drawn", "or", "pulled", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 807, "answer": "I have a baby book that I started writing in as soon as I could kind of spell in which I -- I say I want to be an actress.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "baby", "book", "that", "I", "started", "writing", "in", "as", "soon", "as", "I", "could", "kind", "of", "spell", "in", "which", "I", "--", "I", "say", "I", "want", "to", "be", "an", "actress", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "Did you -- anyone say to you this has Oscar potential?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "--", "anyone", "say", "to", "you", "this", "has", "Oscar", "potential", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "No, but there's something about really good material that you feel like a squirrel with a nut in your cheek, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "there", "'s", "something", "about", "really", "good", "material", "that", "you", "feel", "like", "a", "squirrel", "with", "a", "nut", "in", "your", "cheek", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "do you want to do it?", "question_tokens": ["do", "you", "want", "to", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "Well, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 852, "question": "Do you remember winning?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "winning", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 853, "answer": "On \"The Oriental.\"", "answer_tokens": ["On", "``", "The", "Oriental", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 868, "question": "What did your dad say to you after you won, do you remember?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "your", "dad", "say", "to", "you", "after", "you", "won", ",", "do", "you", "remember", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 869, "answer": "He was happy.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "happy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 894, "question": "How come?", "question_tokens": ["How", "come", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 895, "answer": "You aren't tough enough.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", "n't", "tough", "enough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 910, "question": "What has happened that we are fighting again for reproductive rights in America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "happened", "that", "we", "are", "fighting", "again", "for", "reproductive", "rights", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 911, "answer": "Unbelievable.", "answer_tokens": ["Unbelievable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]